Game: Dai Gyakuten Saiban: Naruhodō Ryūnosuke no Bōken (DGS)
Developer: Capcom
Character: Sherlock Holmes

The AA meshes come with black outline models that require the "backface culling" setting enabled in your 3d program of choice in order to be viewed properly.
Flat style shading is also recommended to get the desired rendering results.

Props:
Pipe: ID_6
Goggles up: ID_10/ID_70/ID_71
Goggles down: ID_13/ID_72/ID_73
Bag: ID_7/ID_16/ID_101

Ripped by qosic / Credit unncessary
Many thanks to this tutorial by "Captain Swag" which was the process I used: https://youtu.be/7xDCtNSXxsA 
Do with these what you will as long as it is within the scope of the law!

